securereservation.net 2012-11-14

# Privacy Policy - SecureReservation.net DHD Hospitality

We highly value your trust in choosing DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net) for your online hotel reservation. Therefore, we will duly and diligently safeguard and protect the privacy and confidentiality of your personal details (including your credit card details).

This privacy policy applies to all of our services (whether accessed or made available online or through any other platform or device (hereafter collectively referred to as the "website")).

**Information Collection**  
When you make a reservation for a hotel (or any other type of accommodation), you will be asked to complete online forms providing: your name, (home or office) address, (business or private) email address, (cell, home or office) telephone number, credit card details (i.e. credit card type and number, CVC code, expiration date, credit card holder name) and to the extent available, reservation preferences and smoking preference. This information is required to process, book and complete your reservation (including the sending of a confirmation email of the booking to you).

**Disclosure of Personal Details**  
For our services, we shall collect for the following purposes the following information:

Reservation Orders: For the purposes of completing your booking and save for disclosures required by law, criminal investigations, subpoenas or court orders, we will only disclose your name, contact details and the credit card details to the relevant hotel with which a booking is made. However, please note that from time to time, we may use third party distributors which provide certain services and functions for and on our behalf. These third party distributors may have access to (part of your) personal information in order to perform their services and functions, but are subject to a confidentiality obligation pursuant to which they cannot use, share or disclose the information for any other purpose.

Surveys: By completing a booking, you agree to receive an email with an invitation to complete our guest review form. We send you this email shortly after your stay at the hotel, and the guest review form can be completed anonymously. By completing the guest review, you agree that the completed guest review can be uploaded to and used on our website on the relevant hotel information page and on such other platforms and social media (wholly or partly) owned, controlled, managed or hosted by us or our trusted business partners for the sole purpose of informing (future) customers on the service (level) and quality of the relevant hotel. We reserve the right to adjust, refuse or remove review forms at our sole discretion. The guest review form should be regarded as a survey and does not include any (further commercial) offers, invitations or incentives whatsoever.

Newsletters and Other Information: If you would like to subscribe to our newsletter or would like to receive promotional communications or other information from us (in respect to our affiliated companies' or business partners' products or services), we offer you the option to "Opt in" for this service. If you no longer want to receive our newsletter and other promotional communications, you can simply click on the unsubscribe link.

Visitor's registration, log in and use of "cookies" and web beacons: For (improvement of) our service and product, we use (temporary and persistent) cookies, authorized third parties cookies, web beacons and/or other technologies to collect non-personally identifiable data such as IP address, browser type and Internet Service Provider (ISP) and (for users of our service through a mobile device) Unique Device Identifier, Operating System and Latitude/Longitude (the "Non-PII"). This non-personally identifiable data helps us to track browsing behavior, to create specific or tailor-made offers or advertisements, and to monitor and record the visits and use of our website(s).

In order to understand how people use our website and for marketing analysis and quality improvement purposes, we collect, record, process and use various data and information on an anonymous basis, such as the total amount of transactions, viewed web pages, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp information and details like the number and location of (mouse) clicks on a given page, mouse movements, scrolling activity and the (search) words used and the text typed while being on and using our website (the "Data").

Furthermore, we will use Non-PII for behavioral targeting. We will also maintain a record of Non-PII for the purposes of potential legal investigations involving fraud, misuse and criminal investigation.

Please note that from time to time, we may use third party service providers for marketing analysis and quality improvement purposes (the "Service Providers"). We may also use Service Providers to track detailed visitor activity on specific pages. These Service Providers collect, use, monitor and report on the Data and other information and statistics, and they analyze online activities on our website. The information about your use of our website (including the Data, your Non-PII) may be transmitted to and stored on the servers of the Service Providers. Furthermore, the Service Providers may also transfer the collected information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on the Service Provider's behalf.

When visiting and using our website, we do not share any personal information about our customers with our Service Providers and the Service Providers will not collect any personally identifiable information ("PII"). PII does not include your IP address, browser type, Internet Service Provider , Unique Device Identifier, Operating System and Latitude/Longitude. We may share and disclose your personal details and information to a governmental or investigative authority if required by law (or any regulation having the force of law), legal process, criminal investigation, court order or subpoena.

About Cookies and Web Beacons: Cookies are text files stored in your computer, either temporarily or persistently on your hard drive. Cookies are used for authenticating, session tracking (state maintenance) and maintaining specific information on the use and users of our website, such as site preferences or the contents of electronic shopping carts. Cookie files may also be placed in your computer by our trusted third-party advertising companies for the purposes as set out in this paragraph. The data collected by these cookies are completely anonymous. If you prefer, you can delete all cookies that are already on your computer's hard drive by searching for files with "cookie" in them and delete them, and for the future, you can edit your browser options such that (future) cookies are blocked; however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of our website. For more information about (the use and decline of) cookies, please visit: www.allaboutcookies.org

Web beacons consist of a small string of software code that represents a graphic image request on a Web page or email. There may or may not be a visible graphic image associated with the web beacon and often the image is designed to blend into the background of a Web page or email. Web beacons can be used for many purposes - including site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, and personalization. Web beacons used by DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net) collect only anonymous data.

**Protect and safeguard your online privacy**  
Please note that, in accordance with European personal data protection laws, strict security procedures are observed within DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net) to prevent personal data misuse and unauthorized access.

DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net) uses trusted and recognized advertising online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards. Most of these companies are a member of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"). The NAI members participate fully in the NAI Principles and offer a general opt-out function of the behavioral advertising. Please visit www.networkadvertising.org to identify the NAI members that have placed an advertising cookie file on your computer. To opt out of an NAI member's behavioral advertising program, simply check the box that corresponds to the company from which you wish to opt out.

Please note that opting out of a network does not mean you will no longer receive or be subject to online advertising or marketing analysis. It does mean that the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your web preferences and usage patterns.

Protect and secure your credit card information  
In order to protect and safeguard the personal data provided to us, we have implemented and use appropriate business systems and procedures. For example, your credit card information is transmitted to us through a secure server protocol, which encrypts all your personal and credit card details. The encryption method used is the industry standard "Secure Socket Layer" (SSL) technology. Our SSL certificate has been issued by Thawte: www.thawte.com   
Furthermore, we have implemented and use security procedures and technical and physical restrictions for accessing and using personal information. Only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information for performing their duties in respect to our services.

Our server and network are protected by firewalls against unauthorized access and we have intrusion detection systems that monitor and detect unauthorized (attempts to) access or misuse our servers.

Your credit card details will be kept by us up to a maximum of 10 days after a booking is made. After that period, your credit card data will be deleted.

**Control over your data**  
You always have the right to review the personal data you have stored with us. You can request your personal data by emailing us at: customer.service@DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net)   
Please state 'request personal data' in the subject line of your email.

If your personal data is incorrect, we will change it upon your request. You can also ask DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net) to remove your personal data from its database by sending us an email to the aforementioned email address.

When does DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net) send you emails?  
After you have made a booking, you will receive a confirmation message with all the information about your booking. You may take this confirmation to the hotel as proof of the reservation. Shortly prior to your arrival date we may send you an email which may include information on your destination and may provide certain information and offers (including third party offers to the extent that you have actively opted in for this information) relevant to your booking and destination. Furthermore, after your stay at the hotel, we will send you the guest review survey, which we appreciate you filling in. Your completed guest review form may be uploaded onto and used on the relevant hotel's information page on our website and on such other platforms and social media (wholly or partly) owned, controlled, managed or hosted by us or our trusted business partners for the sole purpose of informing (future) customers of your opinion of the service (level) and quality of the hotel. To the extent that you have "Opted in" you may receive our newsletter or other information.

**Contact**  
DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net) B.V. is the responsible party for the processing of the personal data. DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net) B.V. is a private limited liability company, incorporated under the laws of the Netherlands and has its offices at Weteringschans 28, 1017 SG, Amsterdam, the Netherlands. The Dutch Data Protection Authority Notification number is 1288246.

If you have any suggestions or remarks about this privacy statement, please send an email to: customer.service@DHD Hospitality Inc (securereservation.net)

We are at all times entitled to change the way we collect, transmit and process personal information and such other information as we may deem necessary. This Privacy Statement may therefore be amended from time to time in order to reflect the latest changes.
